Kenichi Shibata

Architect/Developer

Development/Architecting Scalable and Flexible Systems using MicroService Philosophy and Developing Infrastructure. Great at system planning and implementation. Has good knowledge of best practices in Software Engineering and project management. Can learn and adapt to new programming languages and frameworks. Experienced goal-setter and acts with a clear goal in accordance to company objectives in line with self motivation. Born leader with a desire to enrich people's lives through technology

Phone: +8108034476775

Website: me.kenichishibata.net

Email: kenichi.shibata3123@gm

ail.com

EXPERIENCE

Fast Retailing

Full Stack Engineer

AWS Architect/ Full stack Javascript Engineer

AUGUST 2015 - PRESENT (1 YEAR 3 MONTHS)

Infrastructure: Unix, Bash Scripting, Linux, AWS Cloud, GCloud (Basic) Project Management: Product Development, Architecture (AWS,Akamai), Code Review, Agile, Build Engineering Cl/CD, (Wercker, Jenkins, CodeShip, CircleCl) Back EndDevelopment: PHP Node JS Express JS Restify. AWS Lambda Function Development.

Front End Development: React JS, HTML5, CSS3, Jade, Material UI, Bootstrap, React

Databases: MongoDB, DynamoDB, MySQL

Architecture: AWS, Akamai

Tools: Atom, Sublime, Nginx, Apache, Postman, Box, Dropbox, Slack, *nix, Github, Gitlab, Pivotal Tracker, Trello, Markdown AWS: SNS, SQS, Lambda, EC2, DynamoDB,

Elastic Cache

Architecting Scaleable and Flexible Systems using MicroService Philosophy Develop Restful APIs using AWS services and NodeJS with Restify Framework In charge of Wishlist APIGlobal Ecommerce Development, Rollout, Architecture and cross region distribution Image processing using NodeJS

McVill Cinematography

NOVEMBER 2014 - MAY 2015 (7

MONTHS)

Full Stack Web Developer

Full Stack Web Development (PHP, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL) using LAMP/XAMPP Stack including but not limited to Front End Web Development, Back End Web Development. Web deployment. Database Administration. Infrastructure Management. Web Maintenance.

TypeJump

JUNE 2014 - OCTOBER 2014 (5 MONTHS)

Technical Consultant

Web Development and Technical Consulting

EDUCATION

Bicol University

2009 - 2015

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Science,

Activities and Societies: College Student Council

LANGUAGES

English (Native or bilingual proficiency), Filipino (Native or bilingual proficiency), Bikol (Native or bilingual proficiency), Japanese (Elementary proficiency)

SKILLS

Web Development, Node.js, Project Management, Customer Service, English, Windows, Linux, Management, Amazon Web Services (AWS), JavaScript, CSS, Leadership, Agile Methodologies, Git, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), E-commerce